<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>KDEVO • Kai Dinghofer</title><link>https://kdevo.github.io/</link><description>Recent content on KDEVO • Kai Dinghofer</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 03 Jun 2021 18:05:19 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://kdevo.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Kai Dinghofer</title><link>https://kdevo.github.io/gallery/kd/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2019 22:25:16 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://kdevo.github.io/gallery/kd/</guid><description>&amp;hellip; besides being a free-minded software engineer, I am also a regular human!
I like to travel, take photos and crusing with my skateboard(s) whenever it is possible. Other hobbies include (but are not limited to) running, hiking and of course: diving.
While I love communicating and intuitively connecting with people, it is an equal important part of me having the possibility to relax my mind exploring the world&amp;rsquo;s wonderful nature.</description></item><item><title>Bachelor Thesis</title><link>https://kdevo.github.io/gallery/bachelor-thesis/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2019 22:25:02 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://kdevo.github.io/gallery/bachelor-thesis/</guid><description>About one year after my Bachelor graduation, I asked myself: Why shouldn&amp;rsquo;t other people have the possibility to read my thesis?
In my work, I analyzed how well the Ethereum Blockchain can be integrated into exisiting business processes of the FH Aachen. As a business process execution engine, I used the Open-Source Camunda BPM and wrote an own web3-connector to communicate with self-developed Smart Contracts.
If you like my thesis, please consider a ☕ donation to my Ethereum address:</description></item><item><title>Master Thesis</title><link>https://kdevo.github.io/gallery/master-thesis/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Jun 2021 18:05:19 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://kdevo.github.io/gallery/master-thesis/</guid><description>In my master&amp;rsquo;s thesis, I took a deep dive into the data science world and the emerging field of Reciprocal Recommender Systems (RRSs) which enable Human-to-Human recommendations.
I engineered Chaos, a first of its kind framework that aims to build a solid bridge between the research and development departments of RRSs.</description></item><item><title>Open Argon</title><link>https://kdevo.github.io/gallery/open-argon/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Oct 2020 07:48:28 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://kdevo.github.io/gallery/open-argon/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Grapresso</title><link>https://kdevo.github.io/gallery/grapresso/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2019 13:14:14 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://kdevo.github.io/gallery/grapresso/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Osprey Delight</title><link>https://kdevo.github.io/gallery/osprey-delight/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2019 22:37:07 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://kdevo.github.io/gallery/osprey-delight/</guid><description>{github-description}</description></item><item><title>Hugo Community Mods</title><link>https://kdevo.github.io/gallery/hugo-mods/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 May 2021 23:12:48 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://kdevo.github.io/gallery/hugo-mods/</guid><description>A GitHub organization dedicated to High-Quality Hugo modules, some of them include:
lazyimg: Responsive lazy image loading module with superpowers. Automatically resizes assets, with LQIP and WebP support (plus sane fallback).
icons: SVG symbol icon system, collects only the icons you really use on your site. Designed to be flexible and extensible. Finally, an icon module that scales.
release-notify: Notifies the user whenever a new module release is available.</description></item><item><title>Pyotek</title><link>https://kdevo.github.io/gallery/pyotek/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2019 21:57:17 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://kdevo.github.io/gallery/pyotek/</guid><description>Pyotek is an organization that is still building up. Let&amp;rsquo;s see what the future will bring.
Fow now, you can check out the official non-profit tech-blog! 📰</description></item><item><title>About</title><link>https://kdevo.github.io/about/</link><pubDate>Sat, 23 Oct 2021 16:32:06 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://kdevo.github.io/about/</guid><description>I am a free-minded and passionate software engineer, tech enthusiast and maker, who never stops developing and evolving: You can call me kdevo, too.
By the start of 2021, I&amp;rsquo;ve finished my M.Eng. in Information Systems Engineering at the FH Aachen, where I took a deep dive into the emerging field of Reciprocal Recommender Systems from a research and practical point of view. Bringing these two views together, you can now read my published thesis or experiment with Chaos, a first of its kind framework for researching human-to-human recommendations.</description></item></channel></rss>